[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which domain name is owned by Spain?", "correct_answer": ".es", "incorrect_answers": ["Spain is the only country without a national domain", ".sp", ".hi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens on the quay in the movie The Notebook, when Allie and Noah return from the boat ride in the heavy rain?", "correct_answer": "Noah Kisses Allie.", "incorrect_answers": ["Allie bursts into tears.", "Noah jumps off the quay.", "Allie kisses Noah."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What do megabats, also called flying foxes, feed on?", "correct_answer": "Fruit and nectar", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Carrion", "Insects"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What European country was affected the worst by the European Heat Wave of 2003?", "correct_answer": "France", "incorrect_answers": ["Italy", "Germany", "Spain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the last name of Benjamin and his family in the 1967 movie The Graduate?", "correct_answer": "Braddock", "incorrect_answers": ["Bradley", "Hoffman", "Robinson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the popular names Joseph, Josephine, Jose, Josef, Joe, Joey?", "correct_answer": "The Lord will add.", "incorrect_answers": ["The Lord is merciful.", "The Lord is with us.", "The Lord loves us."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Montgomery is the capital city of this US state, and its largest city is Birmingham.", "correct_answer": "Alabama", "incorrect_answers": ["Arizona", "Alaska", "Arkansas"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In The Dirty Dozen, Samson Posey was played by Clint Walker.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the film Red Dawn, during his lesson, the teacher said that the armies would form a semi-circle around their enemies, about the size of what U.S. state?", "correct_answer": "Rhode Island", "incorrect_answers": ["Delaware", "Vermont", "New Hampshire"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Man On The Moon, Amadeus and One Flew Over the Cuckoos Nest are all movies directed by him.", "correct_answer": "Milo\u0161 Forman", "incorrect_answers": ["Stanley Kubrick", "Pedro Almod\u00f3var", "Martin Scorsese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The flow of the water over the American Falls was completely blocked from June to November in what year?", "correct_answer": "1969", "incorrect_answers": ["1942", "1983", "1936"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the Clark Gable movie that John Dillinger and Anna Sage are watching together in the Biograph Theater in the 2009 Public Enemies movie?", "correct_answer": "Manhattan Melodrama", "incorrect_answers": ["Men in White", "The Call of the Wild", "Dancing Lady"]}]